minifreelancejobs.com 2012-07-21

# Privacy Policy

In minifreelancejobs.com we respect your privacy as we understand and share your concern about the privacy of your personal information. This notice describes our privacy policies. By visiting minifreelancejobs.com, you are confirming your agreement to the privacy policies described in this Privacy Policy Statement.   
This Privacy Policy Statement describes how your personal information will be collected and used by this website in order to provide our service in an efficient and effective way. Please note that it applies only to the minifreelancejobs.com website. Any other websites may refer to different private policies. 

**What personal information is collected?**

One goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide an efficient, meaningful, and customized experience. You can browse minifreelancejobs.com without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers. We may collect and store the following personal information:   
\- name, last name, phone number, mail address, e-mail address   
\- transactional information based on your activities on the website (such as buying products or content   
related to your account)   
\- shipping, billing and other information you provide to purchase or ship an item   
\- other information, including IP address and standard web log information  
If you use the Live Help on our website, it is important that you are aware that any personal identifiable information you submit can be read, collected or used by our Customer Service representatives. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums and we strongly recommend not to provide any financial information, credit card information or passwords. 

**How does minifreelancejobs.com protect customer information?**

When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access. 

**Will minifreelancejobs.com disclose the information it collects to outside parties?**

minifreelancejobs.com won't sell, rent or share in any way your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Occasionally we may send you an email regarding a special promotion that we are running, but you can tell us not to by sending a e-mail message stating for us to remove you from our e-mail list to minifreelancejobs@hotmail.com. 

**how to Update or Access your Personal Information?**

You can access and/or update your personal information at any time. To do that you need to login to your account (http://minifreelancejobs.com/my-account.php) and click the My personal info or My addresses to update your personal information. 

**What about "cookies"?**

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use all of the features in our store, including placing items in your shopping cart and purchasing them. 

**Send to a friend**

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site or products, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit our site. minifreelancejobs.com does not store this information and we will use it for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

**In summary**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect on the site to make shopping at minifreelancejobs.com possible and to enhance your overall shopping experience. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others without your prior consent. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact minifreelancejobs@hotmail.com.
